okay so you're under arrest for section 44 of the of the serious crime act 2007 and section one
what are those sections your shoes on there yeah yeah you just put your shoes on there
if you put your shoes on there you put it up once you saw we're recording why do you need to cover
your face you're officer of the law okay you're doing the right thing is this on
if you're not proud of what you're doing why are you covering your face
we're transporting you okay i'm going to hanker you to the front all right so what you need to do
hatfield police station we discussed that all right when you put your hands like that all right
see that now why are you covering your faces you guys look like gangsters are you gang members
intimidation are you scared of accountability what's yours you want to unzip your vest 159
159 amazing cool okay you taking that to hatfield you said yes yeah gentlemen to know what you've
been arrested i even forgot can you repeat it okay so you're under arrest for section 44 of the of the
serious crime act 2007 and section one or other section second what are those sections section 44
of the serious crime act 2007 it's about um encouraging people to commit crime and the
the other one is section one of the terrorism act okay and that's about um how did i encourage you to
do so we're going to talk about that in the police this year we have to sit in the room no no to arrest
you but we can't interview until you've got to a police station you've been repeat the line that
you used to arrest me booked into custody okay and then given access to a lawyer so we'll repeat the
line that you used to arrest i've already you've already been told what you've been arrested for
okay well well i've just told you and you've just recorded it you've only mentioned you didn't
mention both of them yes i did you mentioned the first one yes i did i i i said two things
i said two offenses play it back bud okay i don't need to keep saying it it's not hard
it's not it's like it's essentially your job you're arresting a young girl and and and and she's been told
what she's been arrested for and she's allowed me to tell you so i mean she said very innocently that she's
she's not i need to keep repeating myself bud do i no you're just kidding a bit thank you
okay